AGNIUS ŽUKAS

Senior Software Engineer

Mobile: 236 862 6089

Email: agniuszu@gmail.com

Location: Vancouver, Canada

Profile

Senior software engineer with a demonstrated 6+ years history of working in different industries. Extensive expertise in large and small system architecture designing and development. Positivity, knowledge sharing, responsibility and lead the way attitude these are the values I strive for every day.

Programming Languages

C#

SQL

Javascript

Go

Python

Technical Skills

.NET core Framework

MS SQL

React.js

OpenShift

MS Business Intelligence tools

Experience

Senior Software engineer, DANSKE BANK A/S

2018-2020

- Developing REST API's using .NET and .NET core framework;
- Participating in designing new solutions based on business needs:
- Creating Web application based on React.js library;
- Responsible for setting up and managing infrastructure for the new project using Openshift and in house cloud solutions;
- Constantly improving performance and solving various issues on existing solutions;
- Participating in technical interview for finding new teammates

Software developer, ATEA Ltd.

2014-2018

- Developing and administering SQL databases:
- Developing web applications in ASP.NET MVC;
- Creating Business Intelligence solutions with Microsoft Business suite:
- Maintaining applications and solving newly arisen problems with a client's help

Software developer, ELGAMA-ELEKTRONIKA Ltd.

2014

- Developing and maintaining testing system (Python);
- Developing and improving software used in manufacture processes (.NET);
- Electricity meters testing;
- Software/Firmware testing

Wireless hardware testing specialist, WILIBOX Ltd.

2013

- Creating new testing scripts and integrating them into general testing environment (Python);
- Solving problems arisen from customers with faulty hardware:
- Maintaining calibration procedures and modifying/creating calibrations software for new devices;
- Hardware testing;
- Measuring devices characteristics of devices

Language Skills

Lithuanian

English

German

Russian

Certifications

MCSA: SQL Server 2012/2014 - Certified 2018

MCSD: App Builder — Certified 2016;

MCPS: Microsoft Certified Professional

MS: Programming in HTML5 with JavaScript and CSS3

MCSD: Web Applications

Education

BA in Electronics Engineering, 2009-2013 Kauno Technologijos Universitetas

Majored in Intellectual Electronics Systems

Young physicist school "Photon", Siauliai University, Faculty of Technology 2006-2009

Personal qualities

- Quickly and easily master new information;
- Strong skills in communicating with personalities of different perspectives and mindsets;
- Able to work independently as well as in a team;
- A great sense of responsibility;
- Eager to learn new things

Interests

Enjoy sports, traveling, reading, big history fan